<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Beacon on </title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/devlog/beacon/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Beacon on </description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright> </copyright>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/devlog/beacon/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Beacon - a new beginning</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/devlog/beacon/a-new-beginning/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/devlog/beacon/a-new-beginning/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;You can find the download for the project in the &amp;lsquo;Projects&amp;rsquo; page on this site or by &lt;a href=&#34;https://jrocg.itch.io/beacon&#34;&gt;clicking this link&lt;/a&gt;, give it a try and let me know what you think!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Beacon started life as a Global Game Jam project that I worked with a group of friends on, you can find that link &lt;a href=&#34;link:&#34; title=&#34;https://globalgamejam.org/2018/games/beacon-0&#34;&gt;here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;the-beginning&#34;&gt;The beginning&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Ever since that project, Beacon became my sort of &amp;ldquo;Hello World&amp;rdquo; game when starting to learn a new game engine. The scope itself is simple yet teaches a lot with lighting, controls, collision, and a bunch of other core skills that can be expanded on in any sort of way. For fun I shared a prototype with a friend I threw together one weekend when really trying to learn Godot and the feedback was far more positive than I expected. From there I decided, yeah I will turn this into a full game.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Development Continues</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/devlog/beacon/development-continues/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/devlog/beacon/development-continues/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;After my last post I became more motivated than ever to continue working on this project. The focus of this &amp;ldquo;sprint&amp;rdquo; so to speak is to clean up the UI as well as add some accessibility features in allowing the user to map their own controls.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Why the focus in UI so early in development? Great question dear reader, while yes I did get a basic outline that works I would have a hard time saying that it is scalable in both the developer time to create a new UI and screen resolution.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
